# **Mateusz**

## Wróbel

### Expertise Area

- Python
- Tkinter
- Ubuntu
- Teamwork
- SQL
- HTML
- Communication
- Customer Experience
- Financial Analysis
- Django
- JavaScript
- CSS



## Summary

I graduated from the Cracow University of Economics in the field of Applied Computer Science. For the last 4 years I have been working in a bank branch. My goal is to find a job in a reputable company where I will be able to improve my knowledge and skills in the field of data analyst. I have "Data Analyst Associate" certificate from datacamp.com I'm in progress "Data Analyst Professional" and Linux Foundation Certified System Administrator.

## Selected Achievements

- I was successively generating 5-10% of the company's monthly income, consisting of about 110 employees in 12 different branches.
- I regularly made a sales plan at the level of 100-120%, which resulted in winning many company competitions, i.e. weekend at an exclusive hotel, an additional day off.
- Conscientious and accurate preparation of documents allowed me to achieve 93% error-free credit processes.
- Craft simulator made with python and tkinter. Portfolio website made using HTML/CSS/JS and Django. All my projects are available on my github profile.

## Professional Experience

Adminotaur Sp. Z o o Junior Support Specialist (2022-2023)

- > analyzing and reporting alerts in Icinga2
- taking care of the proper operation of customer infrastructure
- First line of contact with customers
- Solving simple problems with the help of Ubuntu CLI
- >manually adding an AWS instance
- > carrying out simple acuralization of the client's infrastructure

# CMI-Maciej Uhl/Alior Bank Partner <u>Business client advisor</u> (2018 - 2022)

- reacquiring new clients and building long-term relationships with the current ones, e.g. by actively adjusting the product offer to the current and future needs of the client
- realization of individual and team sales goals
- > sale of banking products and services
- >conducting sales talks and cross-selling

#### ITI Neovision(Canal+) <u>Customer retention consultant</u>

(2016-2017)

- >telephone contact with the company's current customers
- > updating services (extending contracts)
- ➤ breaking down objections

"I had the pleasure of being Mateusz's supervisor for several years, from his early days in banking. During this period, Mateusz Wróbel became known as a person who was extremely quick to learn new issues and willing to gain successive levels of experience. In a very short time, he became a fully independent banker, able to carry out all banking processes comprehensively, applying the required procedures, as well as, thanks to his imagination, his ability to anticipate risks, apply non-standard solutions needed in a specific case. In doing so, he was always extremely attentive, focused and committed, resulting in error-free work. Proficiency in navigating the banking IT environment was always an added advantage for Mateusz. He worked well together in a group and was a helpful and supportive person. I fully recommend Mateusz Wróbel as a valuable employee in the banking industry, as well as, knowing his ability to learn in any other industry he wishes to educate himself in. " - Łukasz Rudek

Scrum Master in GlobaLogic (Mateusz's Menager)



#### Cell:

+48 604 718 555

#### Mail:

mateusz.wrobel993@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/mateuszwróbel

#### Github:

https://github.com/MatWro

## Education

- ✓ Cracow University of Economics Master degree , Applied Computer Science (Oct 2017 - Nov 2019)
- ✓ Cracow University of Economics Bachelor degree, Applied Computer Science (Oct 2012 - Nov 2016)
- ✓ Datacamp.com Data Analyst Associate
- ✓ FrontEnd Developer ( <u>HTML/CSS/JS/GIT</u>) CodersLab (2017)

## Languages

- English Limited working proficiency
- German Elementary proficiency
- Polish Native

## Interested

- x MMO RPG games
- x football
- x cooking